我幻想这事有好几个月了
I have been fantasizing about this for months.
得了  我们来这不是干闲事的
Forget it. We're not here to fool around.
这可不是闲事
I'm not fooling around.
我需要这个
I need this.
你就是个傻子  你知道不
You're an idiot. You know that?
闭嘴  帮我上去
Just shut up and give me a boost.
别磨蹭
Hurry your ass up.
有时候  男人有不得不完成的使命
Sometimes a guy's got to do what a guy's got to do.
捷豹一号呼叫控制台
Jaguar one to control.
抱歉有所耽搁
Sorry for the delay.
格伦得解手  人有三急
Glenn had to take a leak. It was unavoidable.
目标区域安全  重复
Target area is clear. Repeat.
确认目标区域安全
Target area confirmed clear.
李博士  目标区域已清空
Dr. Lee, target area is cleared.
发射装置已就位  一切就绪
Launch vehicle's in range. All systems go.
谢谢  塞萨尔  你准备好就可以开始了
Thank you, Cesar. Whenever you're ready.
CT-10非常轻  无人机也可发射
The CT-10's light enough to launch from a UAV,
爆炸前  可穿透抗压强度约四万兆帕
but can penetrate 8 feet of 6,000-psi concrete
厚达八英尺的混凝土层
before detonation.
炸弹已发射
Bomb's away.
精确制导系统不受光线和气象影响
Precision guidance system's not affected
并能从六万九千英尺的高空
by darkness or weather and can hit
狙击两英寸大小的目标
a 2-foot-wide target from 69,000 feet.
声响方面呢
What about sound?
完全监测不到
None inbound at all.
我们开发出一种新风机
We've developed a new fan
以及一种迷惑性设计
and a baffling design that--
击中目标倒数  三  二  一
Ordnance on target in three, two, one.
我感觉好多了
I feel better already.
你需要看心理医生
You need to see a shrink.
说真的
Seriously.
漂亮
Well done.
温迪
Wendy!
叫救护车
Call 911!
因果报应
Karma's a bitch.
你觉得她癫痫发作是报应
You think her seizures are the result of bad karma?
我觉得要是你把时间全花在
I think if you spend your days
如何更精准的炸飞别人这件事上
designing ever more effective ways to blow people up,
早晚遭天谴
stuff's bound to come back to you.
口渴
Thirsty.
我刚用上的抗组胺药的副作用
Side effect of a new antihistamine I'm on.
看不出你有局部充血啊
You don't seem congested.
有意思
Intriguing.
你对这个病人有什么想法
You have any thoughts about our patient?
对十三是真相信还是只是强迫自己相信
Got some questions about whether Thirteen
因果报应这个事  倒是有些疑问
really believes in karma or just wants to.
至于病人
As for the patient,
要闯入她办公室肯定不容易
it's not gonna be easy to break into her office.
那就从她家开始
Might want to start with her home.
我们可征求同意  再查看她的办公室
We could ask to look through her office
同时先给她做核磁共振
and we could do an MRI first.
行  去吧
Sure. Go ahead.
你要是对这个病例没兴趣
If you're not interested in the case,
为什么要接呢
why'd you take it?
我当然感兴趣
I am definitely interested.
可能是肿瘤  可能是颅内出血
Could be a tumor. Could be a cns bleed.
两个谜题待你解答  还有何求
What do you do when you got two interesting puzzles?
两个
Two?
50块
50 bucks!
给钱
Pay up.
快给  快给
Let's go. Let's go.
这赌不算
Bet's off.
有人操控比赛结果
Fight was fixed.
那一拳都没打到他
That punch barely touched him.
你赌福利能打赢扎卡里[拳击手]
You bet on Foley to beat Zachary?
速度型战胜力量型
Speed beats power...
除非有人买通了他
Unless speed has been paid
让他速度地故意输掉
to speedily take a dive.
他被打到的次数不少  承受不了很正常
He touched him enough to put him on the canvas
倒数结束  他还无法站起来
and the official counted him out,
铁证如山  你欠我
which means you officially owe me
50块
50 bucks.
我们赌的是体育赛事
We bet on a sporting event.
那才不是体育
That was not sporting.
都不到30秒
Less than 30 seconds.
都算不上比赛
That was barely even event-y.
我看到的是
Okay, here's what I saw.
你输  我赢
You lost and I won.
行  你就带着这个念头进棺材吧
Yeah, well, you can take that to your grave.
我才不会把那50块给你
You're not taking my 50 bucks.
拿出证据
Prove it.
拿出证据  要么给钱
Prove it or pay up.
你有一天时间
You got one day.
别逼我派我的小鸭子们去找你讨债
And don't make me send my boys out looking for you.
什么
What?
好吧
All right.
话说  有两个谜题
So, two puzzles.
我去解开害我输钱的那个
Tie goes to the one that costs me money.
记得互通进展
Keep each other posted.
我一直很健康
I've always been healthy.
连感冒都没得过
I never even get colds.
看来你的好运到头了
I guess your luck finally ran out.
看来她不喜欢造炸弹的人
I take it she doesn't like people who makes bombs.
抱歉  我不是故意的
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to.
没事
It's all right.
我多半的家人也是这样想的
Half of my family feels the same way.
他们都在华尔街上班  当然会...
Of course they all work on Wall Street, so...
自打我记事开始
Ever since the first 4th of July I can remember,
我就喜欢爆炸
I've always loved explosions.
当我要念大学  选专业时
When I got to college and I had to pick a major,
觉得该选自己热爱的专业
figured I might as well pick something I'm passionate about.
你喜欢摧毁东西
Destroying things.
对其它的都不感兴趣吗
You weren't passionate about anything else?
跟其它事物一样  炸弹只是工具
Bombs are tools, just like anything else.
既有好的一面
You can use it to make things better
也有坏的一面
or you can use it to make things worse.
我也喜欢浪漫诗
I also like romantic poetry
还有野餐
and picnics.
核磁共振前还有什么
Is there anything else you want to know
你们想知道的吗
before we do this MRI?
没了
Nope.
尽量保持静止不动
Try to stay as still as possible.
不会花太久时间
This shouldn't take long.
你好啊
Hey, how's it going?
介意坐其它地方吗
You mind?
那么多空位
I mean, there are plenty of other seats.
我不是来评头论足
I'm not here to judge.
你做了对自己最有利的选择
You did what was best for you
这我没意见
and I got no problem with that.
我最后跟你说一次
I'm not gonna ask you nice again.
-走开  -不然怎样
- Just go away. - Or what?
你还准备把我撂倒吗
Is something gonna fall down?
听着  是这么回事
Listen. I got a problem.
一小子对拳击一窍不通
A guy who knows absolutely nothing about boxing,
因为你  现在他觉得自己是专家
because of you, now thinks he does.
你可以想象后果的严重性
You can imagine the potential ramifications.
我需要你跟他通个电话
I need you to get on the phone with him
告诉他你是故意放水的
and tell him you took a dive.
我并没有故意放水
I didn't take a dive.
再拍个照证明这真是你
Take a picture of you to prove that it was really you
我们就完事了
and we're done.
只为使他信服
Just enough to convince him.
不会让你惹上任何麻烦
Not enough to get you in any trouble.
我没有故意放水
I didn't take a dive.
是
Yeah.
你这个理由可不怎么样
That story's getting boring.
听着  我不是调查局的
Look, I'm not from the commission.
我不是什么赌博经纪人
I'm not some bookie.
我是医生  这是我的证件
I'm a doctor. This is my I.D.
听着  要你真是经纪人
Look, if you were a bookie,
你就会知道没人会贿赂
you'd know no one pays a guy to throw a fight
没机会赢的拳击手
he has no chance to win.
我是个赔率1赔12的废物
I was a 12-to-1 underdog.
过去五场比赛  我都输了
Lost my last five fights.
但你是个很优秀的拳击手啊
But you were the better fighter.
最后那拳几乎都没碰到你
That last punch barely touched you.
你有被一个重达230镑的家伙
You ever been barely touched by a guy
轻轻揍过吗
who weighs 230 pounds?
看看我
Look at me.
看看这个地方  还有我穿的衣服
Look where I am, what I'm wearing.
我像是个刚拿到酬劳的人吗
Now,do I look like a guy who just got a payday?
我没有故意输掉比赛
I didn't throw the fight.
我就是水平太烂
I just suck.
证据在此
Proof.
仅仅因为他没有被打爆脸
Just because he wasn't hit in the face--
看看他的瞳孔
Look at his pupils.
两侧瞳孔不等大  考虑到他的年龄
He has anisocoria, which, given his age,
以及比赛时肾上腺素的激增
the adrenaline surge of the fight,
再加上目前他还活得好好的
the fact that he's still alive
说明他当时心动过速
means he was tachycardic.
他患有WPW综合征
He has Wolff-Parkinson-White syndrome.
我们赌的是谁赢
The bet was on who would win,
而不是谁能活最久
not who would live the longest.
如果他因为身体有病
If he's physically unable to continue
而在体力上不能坚持打完比赛
because of a preexisting illness,
那么严格意义上讲  比赛是无效的
then it's technically a "No contest",
也就是说  我们打的赌是无效的
which means all bets are off.
即使这次拳击赌博是我猜对了
You know that just because I was right
也丝毫不会减弱你的男子气概
about this one fighter doesn't make you
这点你清楚  对吗
any less of a man?
要是你赢了  还真会伤我心肝呢
Actually, it would if you were right.
那就像我之前说的  你拿出证据来
Then as I said earlier, prove it.
一张可能处理过的手机照片
And one possibly photoshopped cell phone pic
不足以成为诊断依据
does not a diagnosis make.
豪斯医生  请等一下
Oh, excuse me, Dr. House.
真抱歉  我不会说英语[法语]
Desole, je parle pas anglais.
我是温迪·李的同事
I'm a co-worker of Wendy Lee's.
也是她的男友
I'm also her boyfriend.
太棒了  我对此毫无兴趣
Great. I'm a guy who doesn't care.
她是你的病人
She's your patient.
你以为我不知道温迪·李是谁吗
Oh, you thought I didn't know who Wendy Lee was?
有点道理  我确实不太擅长记人名
Yeah, makes sense. I'm not good at names.
福运医生[指福曼]跟你提过这点吗
Did Dr. Fortune tell you that?
她的前男友就是个疯子
Her last boyfriend was a real nut.
他一直在跟踪她
He's basically stalking her.
你说的正是我不感兴趣的内容
See, this is what I don't care about.
我才不在乎谁关心她呢
I don't care who cares about her,
也不在乎谁曾经关心过她
used to care about her.
你们俩要是有人挂了  给我留张字条
Either one of you falls down dead, you can drop me a note.
我想我知道她这是怎么回事
I think I know what's wrong with her.
你弄砸了实验
You screwed up in the lab
然后不小心泼了她一身炸药吗
and accidentally spilled some bomb on her?
不是
No.
他确实疯得够呛
He really is crazy.
被人下毒了
Poisoned?
显然咱们疯狂的科学家
Apparently our mad scientist
还是位风情万种的科学家
is also a slutty scientist
能让她身边的呆子
whose milkshakes got all the nerds in the yard
全都为之争风吃醋
fighting over her.
就因为她勾搭了两名同事谈恋爱
She's a slut because she's dated
你就说她放荡吗
two different guys at work?
真抱歉
Oh, I'm sorry.
我以为咱们仍然在对她品头论足呢
I thought we were still judging her.
她不是荡妇  也没被下毒
She's not a slut and it's not poison.
我们检测了她的血液和脑脊液
When we tested her blood and cerebral spinal fluid
没有发现任何我们能想到的
for toxic exposure, it was negative
有毒物质
for every poison we could think of.
看来就只剩下
Well, that just leaves
所有我们没能想到的有毒物质了
every poison we didn't think of.
她在炸弹工厂上班
She works in a bomb factory.
那里也有很多人没生病
So do a lot of other not-sick people.
如果他有她被下毒的真凭实据
The guy had any actual evidence she was poisoned,
就会去找警察  而不是我们了
he would have gone to the police, not to us.
如果有任何有助于诊断的线索
And if we had any evidence of what was wrong with her,
你早就给我们看MRI的结果了
you'd be showing us MRI results.
所以我猜结果是阴性
I assume they were negative.
不妨试试活性炭  看看病人有什么反应
Couldn't hurt to start activated charcoal, see what happens.
知道还有什么也可以不妨一试吗
You know what else wouldn't hurt?
病例是越来越有趣了
This case is getting interesting.
不妨再给它加把劲吧
Let's add a little danger.
仅仅因为他持有枪支
Just because he has guns
并不能证明他就是个凶手
doesn't make him a murderer.
这话你倒是跟这头熊说去
Tell that to the bear.
查查写字台
Look in the desk.
看看他有没有日记或记事簿
See if he's got a diary or a journal.
有迹象表明  他并不是那种
Something tells me he's not exactly
喜欢记日记的人
a diary kind of guy,
赤裸裸的威胁倒有可能
maybe a manifesto.
随便查一下
Just look.
我去检查下其它地方
I'm gonna check out the rest of the place,
看看他有没有电脑
see if he's got a computer.
-福曼打来的  -什么事
- It's Foreman. - Yep?
你们已经进去了吗
You break in yet?
是啊  我们正身处屠宰场呢
Yeah, we're in the abattoir now.
-怎么了  -你们可以撤了
- Why? - You can leave.
我觉得我们已经找到了所需的证据
I think Taub and I found what we're looking for.
看起来她确实一直被人下毒
Looks like she actually was being poisoned,
只不过投毒者正是她自己
but she's been doing it to herself.
-我不酗酒  -我明白
- I'm not an alcoholic. - I know.
你喝酒是有控制的喝
I know the whole label thing is so limiting.
现在只是碰巧酒精中毒而已
You're a person who happens to suffer from alcoholism.
你非法闯入我家
You broke into my house
现在又自作聪明  是吗
and now you're being a smart ass?
你在病史里声称自己滴酒不沾
During your history, you said you didn't drink at all.
我确实不喝酒
I don't.
-你只是收集酒瓶子玩  -是的
- You just collect bottles. - Yes.
那些酒瓶子是给我朋友的
I collect them for my friend.
她要用来做艺术品
She uses them in her art projects.
而这些艺术品让你拿不出手
And you're ashamed of these art projects.
你把瓶子都藏起来了
The bottles were hidden.
那是因为清洁工总是要扔掉它们
That's because my housekeeper keeps throwing them out.
我告诉她无数次了
I've told her a dozen times not to,
她要么没听懂要么压根不在乎
but either she doesn't understand or she doesn't care.
-她干嘛撒谎呢  -没深度的问题
- Why would she lie? - That's the easy question.
她的工作要求她通过政府安全合格认证
She needs a government security clearance for her job.
那什么才是有深度的问题
And what's the hard question?
如果她酗酒  那为什么她家里
If she's an alcoholic, why doesn't she have
一个喝剩下一半的酒瓶都没有呢
at least some partially-full bottles in the house?
我的意思是  干嘛留着空瓶子
I mean, why keep the empties?
干嘛不直接扔掉呢
Why not just throw them away?
也就是说  很有可能她讲的都是实话
So she's probably telling the truth.
那我们怎么办
So what do we do?
使用安定让她戒酒
We start her on valium for alcohol withdrawal.
这是我们目前最好的办法了
It's the best we've got right now.
心电图正常并不代表身体健康
One normal EKG does not a healthy person make.
我说了  我就是水平太烂
Look, I told you I just suck.
你可真让我寒心
Oh, you make me so sad.
别用那种口气跟我说话
Don't talk like that.
你干嘛这么关心我
Why do you care so much?
医生关心病人  天经地义
Kill me for loving my patients.
我就靠这个吃饭呢
It's just what I do.
别走  站住
Hey, stop. Stop!
我的...我腿脚不方便
Look, my--my leg hurts. Okay?
我们好好聊一聊
Just talk to me for a moment.
你不要自暴自弃
You don't have to be a loser.
谢了
Thanks.
不管是什么问题  你的确生病了
Whatever's wrong with you, it's real.
生病是好事
Sick is good.
说明你能好起来
Sick means you can get better.
你能变得更强
You could get better.
我想说的不是你身体会更健康
And I don't mean healthier.
我想说的是
I mean...
或许你的拳击比赛就不会无疾而终
Maybe you don't have to suck.
你还是想想自己有什么毛病吧
Figure out what's wrong with yourself.
别来烦我
Leave me alone.
病人腹痛
Abdominal pain.
她说就好像是被捅了一样疼
She said it felt like she was being stabbed.
静脉注射五毫克吗啡
Give her morphine, 5 milligrams iv.
这是她身上未知疾病的症状
Is it a symptom of the underlying condition,
还是她对我们治疗的反应
or a symptom of our treatment?
很快就能知道了  我已经停了她的治疗
We'll know soon. I stopped her treatment.
应该继续开始
We should restart it.
疼痛可能是由
Acute pancreatitis from alcoholism
酒精中毒诱发的急性胰腺炎引起
would cause this kind of pain.
是压力诱发的
It's stress related.
她正忍受着剧烈疼痛
She's in a lot of pain.
她遭受着巨大压力
She's under a lot of stress.
有两个男人为她争风吃醋
She's got two guys fighting over her
她刚完成了新炸弹的最后测试环节
and she got done with the final test of a new bomb.
罪恶感让她一病不起
Her guilt is killing her.
我倒是觉得  她喜欢成为焦点
As far as you know, she likes being the center
热爱自己的工作
of attention and loves her job.
你也知道她不喝酒吧
As far as you know, she doesn't drink.
如果是肾脏感染吗
What if it's a kidney infection?
不给她静脉滴注抗生素的话
Acute pyelonephritis could kill her
她会死于急性肾盂肾炎
if we don't start her on iv antibiotics.
如果确实是肾盂肾炎的话  她才会
Would kill her if it was pyelonephritis,
但是她的尿液和脑脊液检查
but since her urine and csf
并未显示出感染的迹象
don't show signs of infection--
我呼了豪斯
I paged House.
干嘛这样看我  我们毫无头绪
What? We got nothing.
应该说是更糟  他根本无视我的呼叫
Less than nothing since he's actually ignoring my pages,
也就是说  我们有个病患
which means we have a sick patient
和一个无药可救的老板
and apparently a sick boss.
你去告诉他  你认输了
Tell him you admit he's right.
我们得让他回到工作中来
Let's get him back to work.
他忽略你  是因为他信任你
If he's ignoring you,it's because he trusts you.
不  不是的
No, it's not.
好吧  也许不是  但他确实信任你
No, it's not, but he does.
谢谢  你这么说我真感动
Thanks. I feel warm inside.
我现在正纠结于
Right now I'm debating
该硬着头皮把哪个诊断当作是正确的
which bad idea I should pretend is a good idea
然后强迫其他人去实施
and force everybody to implement.
我觉得这对他有好处
I think this is good for him.
执迷于一个赌博有好处吗
Obsessing over a bet is good?
做好本职工作  治愈病患
And doing his actual job, treating actual patients,
反而是无益的吗
that's bad?
豪斯只会做自己想做的事
House only doing what House wants
他这人就这样
is the only way he can function.
和卡迪分手后  他就开始
Since the breakup, he's been seeking out
不断挑战疯狂的极限
crazier and crazier things to do
就因为这些事很疯狂
because they're crazy.
而这事还不算疯狂
This is--well, it's not crazy.
是不疯狂  就是不负责任又危险罢了
No, just irresponsible and possibly dangerous.
按豪斯的标准来看  这很无趣
By House standards, it's dull.
而他正在琢磨的事情
This he's doing
纯粹是出于兴趣
just because he's interested.
豪斯重操旧业  以令人无语的理由
I think House getting back to doing...
做那些只有他才会做的蠢事
stupid House stuff for stupid House reasons
我觉得这对他来说  是好事
is the best thing that could happen to him.
我等下就这么向病人解释
I'll go explain that to the patient.
绝对不是胰腺炎
It's definitely not pancreatitis.
重新开始治疗并未使病情有所好转
Restarting the treatment obviously didn't help anything.
我猜你做了肾脏感染检查
I assume you tested for infections.
而你的表情告诉我
And I assume that look means
"是的  但我的诊断错了"
"Yes, and I was wrong."
你给病人进行了心理咨询吗
You call for a psych consult?
你的囧样和奇斯还真是一模一样
That's the same look I just got from Chase.
一个小时前  我们有三个诊断
So an hour ago, we had three theories
但我们无法达成一致
we couldn't agree on.
现在我们没有任何诊断  却达成了一致
Now we've got no theories, but we're in agreement.
CT和超声显示
CT and ultrasound showed inflammation
肾被膜下有炎症
in the renal capsule.
可能是结石堵塞
Could be an obstructing calculus
或者是肾周脓肿
or a perinephric abscess.
血培养显示阴性
Blood cultures came back negative.
可能只是个良性肿瘤
It's probably just a benign cyst.
行啊  那我们就因为它可能无碍
Yes, let's just dismiss an idea
就把一种病因排除在外吧
because it's probably nothing.
可能是肾周间隙积气
Could be gas in the perinephric space,
如果这样的话  我们得让她准备好
In which case,we should be prepping her
进行紧急手术
for emergency surgery.
什么病症不是WPW综合征
What looks like wolff-parkinson-white
但看着像WPW综合征呢
but isn't?
-她的心电图显示正常  -我说的是他
- Her EKG was normal. - So was his.
这就是我说"看着像"的原因了
That's why I said "looks like."
也就是说是相似  但不完全一致
As in similar to, but not the same.
你想让我们帮你省下赌债
You want us to help you get out of paying your bet
徒留你真正的病人在痛苦中挣扎
while your actual patient lies in agony.
这里究竟谁才是坏人呢
Who's the real bad guy here?
是那个事不关己袖手旁观的人
The guy who doesn't care enough to help
还是那四个爱莫能助的人呢
or the four guys who are not competent enough to help?
他过度健身  经常挨揍
He works out too much, gets pounded too much,
当然不是情人间的打打闹闹
and not in the romantic way.
-他的眼球...  -我知道了
- His pupils... - I got it.
不是再说你们的病人
Your patient? No.
等你们帮我把钱省下来后
Plenty of time to save her life
有足够的时间去救她
after we save my money.
她的风流韵事导致了急性泌尿系统感染
Underlying neurological condition exacerbated
从而引起了潜在的神经系统问题
by an acute uti brought on by her sexual escapades.
荡妇  风流韵事
Slut? Escapades?
我们怎么治疗呢  给她挂个赤字吗
How do we treat? A scarlet "A"?
抱歉
Sorry.
她过度的性生活
Acute uti brought on
导致了急性泌尿系统感染
by her healthy enjoyment of her womanhood.
我们开始给她静脉滴注氨苄西林
We start her on iv ampicillin
和氨基糖苷类抗生素
and an aminoglycoside.
你经常无视我们
You ignore us all the time.
也会做无厘头的事情
You go on crazy joyrides all the time.
但你会回复呼叫  会睡觉
But you answer pages, you sleep.
我知道我会后悔这么做的
I know I'm gonna regret doing this,
但我还是要问下
but I'll ask anyway.
有什么我可以帮忙的吗
Is there anything I can do to help?
虽然
Although...
好消息
Great news!
你患有某种神经系统疾病
You have an underlying neurological condition,
再考虑到你的心脏问题
which together with your heart--
你说过我的心脏很好
You said my heart was fine.
是的  我还说能让你重振雄风
Yeah, I also said I would get you your career back.
但现在都无关紧要了
But it doesn't seem to matter
因为很明显你自己
since you've so clearly been handed
也准备洗手不干了
the golden spit bucket.
交感神经过度兴奋
Sympathetic overdrive.
是个医学术语
It's a medical term.
"好消息"也是
So is "great news."
当然  你想要堕落的话
Of course, if you prefer wallowing...
咱俩好好谈谈就能解决了
All you need is a chin.
显然  还要有颗心
And a heart, apparently.
你就又是那个开初二十连胜的选手
Then you can go back to being the guy who won 20 of his first 20
而非终了五连败的人了
instead of the guy who lost 5 of his last 5.
不过  准确来说
Although, technically,
我觉得最后一次都算不上是拳击赛
I count the last one as a "no contest."
-你就可以省五十美元了  -我是医生
- And you save 50 bucks. - I'm a doctor.
要想让我来看病  时薪不能小于三百
I don't tell a fat guy to lay off bacon for less than 300.
这事关乎我们两个人的尊严
This is about dignity for both of us.
把你手臂给我
Give me your arm.
怎么回事
What the hell?
不要担心
Don't worry.
肾上腺素而已
It's just epinephrine.
肾上  危险吗
Ep--is it dangerous?
使用不当的话  是很危险
In the wrong hands, very.
所以  是的  有点危险
So...Yeah, sort of.
只要几秒钟就好
This will only take a few seconds.
你心动过速
And... You are tachycardic.
老兄  你疯了吗
Yo, are you psycho?
我应用一些小小的药物手段
We combine the increased heart rate with chest trauma
重现比赛中出现的伴有胸痛的心动过速
by applying a little sweet science to the science.
不要担心
Don't worry.
我  等你醒后我会解释的
I'll-- I'll explain more when you wake up.
现在  我这个老瘸子要挥出一拳
Now, the punch that supposedly knocked you out
应该就可以把你打晕了
looked like it was thrown by an old cripple.
就像这样
Kind of like this.
听着  住手
Look, stop it.
三
Three...
二  一
Two, one.
看来我刚才那拳太弱了点
Seem to be older and more crippled than I thought.
听着  住手  你让我很难堪
Look, no. You're embarrassing me.
说不通啊
Doesn't make sense.
或许要是我
Maybe if I--
别再出现在我眼前  你个疯子
Look, get the hell out of my life, you lunatic.
她发生室性心动过速  血压在往下降
She's in v-tach. BP's dropping.
不管你们采用了什么治疗  还是不管用
Whatever you're doing isn't working again.
总得想办法让癫痫停下来吧
There's got to be some way to stop the seizures.
这并不是癫痫  她心脏病发了
It's not a seizure. She's having a heart attack.
-没有脉搏  -不可能
- No pulse. - That's impossible!
她都能跑马拉松
She runs marathons!
充电到200焦耳  离手
Charging to 200. Clear.
还是没有脉搏
Still no pulse.
充电到300焦耳
Charging to 300.
-怎么会这样  -离手
- Why is this happening? - Clear.
我的理论是他之所以躲着我们
My theory is that he's only avoiding us
是因为他不想见你
because he really wants to avoid you.
[逾越四问]
Ma nishtanah?
你在医学院这么多年就没参加过逾越节吗
You made it through med school without ever attending a Seder?
那句话的意思是  今晚和其它夜晚
It means "Why is this night different
有什么不同呢
from all other nights?"
我也不确定
I'm not sure it is.
但一般事态严重时他都会出现
But usually when push comes to shove, he shows up.
如果病人还活着  那事态还不够严重
If the patient's still alive, then push hasn't met shove yet.
病人已命悬一线
Patient is hanging by a thread
我们确对病因毫无头绪
and we don't have a clue why.
那我们只好假定豪斯胸有成竹
Then we have to assume he does
而病人还能挺住
and she isn't.
话虽如此  我们也可以认为
We could or we could assume that something
豪斯确实出了什么事
is seriously wrong with House
并对此采取些行动
and try to do something about that.
这样即使我们错了  也没人会死
This way, even if we're wrong, nobody dies.
豪斯没事
House is fine.
豪斯总能照顾好自己
House is always fine.
我只是在阐述我的理论
I'm expanding my theory.
他躲着你  你也躲着他
He's avoiding you and you're avoiding him
而这个病人快要死了
and this patient is gonna die.
你要做好本职工作她就不会死
Not if you do your job.
你真是个傻瓜
You're an idiot.
你怎么进来的
How did you get in here?
我老板成天让我非法闯入各种地方
My boss has me break into places all the time.
疼痛越来越严重了
Pain has been getting worse.
我发现如果我再加大维克丁的剂量
I figured if I upped the vicodin any more,
我又得回戒毒所里去了
I'd end up back in a rubber room,
因此这个选择看上去更明智
so this seemed like the smarter choice.
你真是个傻瓜
You're an idiot.
你大老远开过来
You drove all the way over here
闯进我家就为了叫我傻瓜吗
to break in and call me an idiot?
不  我大老远开过来是为了告诉你
No, I drove all the way over here to tell you
我们要在病人体内放置自动心脏除颤仪
we're implanting an automated cardio-defibrillator,
虽然不会对病人有任何帮助
which won't actually do anything to help the patient
但至少能为我们继续猜测她的病因
except maybe give us enough time to come up with a guess
提供足够的时间
as to what's actually wrong with her.
这听上去有道理多了
Oh, that makes more sense.
我之所以闯进来是因为卡迪和威尔森
And I broke in here because Cuddy and Wilson
分别找到我  让我这么做的
both separately asked me to.
更有道理了
Even more logical.
这不是海洛因
And that's not heroin,
就是说你知道我会过来
which means you knew I was coming over here,
而卡迪和威尔森是对的
and Cuddy and Wilson are right.
你只是在耍我们
You're just playing a game.
扔了块骨头想看我们如何你争我夺
Throwing out a bone and watching us fight over it.
还有一个理论
There is another theory.
化合物CS-804
Compound cs-804.
是一种试验药物
It's an experimental drug
理论上可以使肌肉再生
that's supposed to regrow muscle.
这实验是在老鼠身上做的
This experiment was done on rats.
这药取得了突破性进展  是巨大的成功
It's groundbreaking. Huge success.
只是在老鼠上
In rats.
它们还有四条腿呢
Well, they got four legs.
要是只有一条腿的话  岂不是更有效
Think how fast it should work on one.
你真是个傻瓜
You're an idiot.
出问题了
We've got a problem.
除颤仪不工作了吗
AICD not working?
如果是那个问题  我会检查别的部位
If it's the defibrillator, I'd be looking elsewhere.
闻上去像出血
Smells like bleeding.
直肠出血吗
Rectal?
还有阴道出血
And vaginal.
有没有可能是在手术过程中造成了穿孔
Is it possible something got perforated during surgery?
你这是指责吗
Is that an accusation?
更像是提问
Sounded like a question.
就是个简单的问题
Just a straightforward inquiry
只有心里有鬼的人
that only someone with serious insecurities
才会有此疑问吧
would take issue with.
好吧  要回答你这个问题
Okay, so in answering, I have to decide
我只有两种选择
between the only two possibilities.
"没有"以及"没错  我们可能搞砸了
"No." And "Yes, we might have screwed something up,
但却故意隐瞒事实
but are intentionally hiding it
因为我们是不称职的混蛋"
because we're incompetent and we're asses."
我的答案是  没有
Answer is "No."
我们的手术一切正常
Glad we didn't shortchange that avenue.
可能是血液病
It's a blood disorder.
-凝血技能障碍  -那不能作为诊断
- A coagulopathy. - That's not a diagnosis.
那就跟说她在流鼻涕一样太笼统了
That's like saying she has a runny nose.
没错  但如果不擦鼻涕的话
True, but not saying she has a runny nose
就会弄得到处都是  不可收拾
risks getting snot all over us.
-我们可着手治疗  -病因可能还是中毒
- We can treat it. - Cause could still be a toxin.
鬼知道她以前有什么毒物暴露史...
She must have been exposed to who knows--
那也是过去时  就是说她应该有所好转
Past tense, which means she would have been better
但实际没有
now that she's not.
豪斯也一样
Same goes for House.
如果这次是因为卡迪
If this was about Cuddy,
他几周前就该这样了
he would have checked out weeks ago.
肯定发生了什么新的问题
Something else is going on. Something new.
他这是感情问题处理不好的正常表现
That's an awfully simplistic approach to matters of the heart.
豪斯是理智的  他很得意于此
House is rational. He prides himself--
没人能理智地处理感情
No one is rational about emotion.
这也是感情被称为感情的原因
That's why they're emotions.
你觉得呢
What do you think?
-我  我什么都没说  -正是如此
- Me? I didn't say anything. - Exactly.
对这类事你总有自己的见解
You always have some opinion on these things,
尤其是对豪斯
especially when it comes to House,
谈及男人加上感情  你更是如此
double especially when it comes to men and romance,
但突然间你却如此沉默
but suddenly you're keeping your mouth shut.
豪斯帮不了我们
House can't help us.
无论有多蠢  我都尊重他的隐私
I respect his privacy, no matter how stupid and
我希望你们也能尊重我的隐私
I'd appreciate it if you'd respect mine.
我们需要对症下药才行
We need to treat the underlying condition.
可能是癌症  败血症  创伤
Could be cancer, sepsis, trauma,
肝病  出血热
liver disease, hemorrhagic fever--
我要去对症治疗了
I'm gonna start treating the symptoms
你就慢慢列出所有可能的病因吧
while you finish listing the possible causes.
老鼠的实验结果不错
The rats are doing great.
"不错"这说法有点含糊不清
"Great" is a little vague.
比以前的研究成果要好
Even better than the previous study.
力量加强了12%
12% increase in strength,
灵活度增强了22%
22% in flexibility, and some improvement
至少60%的实验鼠都有所改善
in at least 60% of the subjects.
你做最大耐药性的实验了吗
Have you done maximum tolerated dose studies?
还没
Not yet.
但这正是这种药物的美妙之处
But that's part of the beauty.
这种化合物很容易从尿中排出
Since the compound is easily excreted in urine,
因此只要别让他们脱水
as long as they keep hydrated,
理论上任何剂量都应该
there's really no reason to expect any danger
没什么危险
at virtually any dose.
我的意思是  很明显谁也不敢打包票
I mean, obviously you can't know for sure.
但如果用上了"明显"这种词
But if it's worthy of the preface "obviously,"
那很明显  只要向傻瓜解释就行
then obviously it only needs to be explained to idiots.
我像傻瓜吗
Do I look like an idiot?
不好意思
Sorry.
我心情不好
Cranky.
我的意思是说
What I meant to say was:
为什么科学家们没有粉丝团呢
Why don't scientists have groupies?
如果没人告诉我你只是个拿薪水的呆子
'cause I'd do you right now if society wasn't telling me
我一定会疯狂的崇拜你的
that you're just an underpaid dork.
谢谢
Thank you.
你还好吗
You all right?
腿疼
Leg hurts.
你能给我拿杯咖啡吗
Would you mind getting me a coffee?
咖啡能减缓你的腿部疼痛吗
How does coffee help your leg?
至少能让我免去拿咖啡的这段路
It will prevent me from walking to get the coffee.
好吧
Right.
呼叫上说她嘴里开始流血了
Page said she's now bleeding from her mouth.
你开始治疗了吗
You start treatment?
我说过我会开始治疗
I said I would.
直接回答"是"就可以了
A "Yes" would have been fine.
你别问这问题更好
Not asking the question would have been even better.
有呼吸问题吗
Any breathing issues?
没有  但是
No, but--
我感觉不是腹部问题
I'm not sure it's internal.
如果是从两边开始  就是腹部问题
If it's coming from both ends, it's internal.
她的牙龈看起来像是被烫伤了
Her gums look like they were burned.
你在用试验性药物吗
Experimental drugs?
你这么说不公平
That's unfair.
因为就算是维柯丁  也是试验性药物
Because at one point, even Vicodin was an experimental drug.
我得走了
I have to go.
除非你要去上班
Well,unless you're going to do your job,
-其它的事可以等等  -我是要去上班
- it can wait. - I'm going to do my job.
那我开车送你去
I'll give you a lift.
我就给你两分钟
I'll give you two minutes.
但是首先我要告诉你  我停用那种药了
But first, I'm gonna tell you that I'm off the drugs,
之后你会感觉你很傻
and you'll feel silly
因为你不知道接下来两分钟你要说什么
'cause you've got nothing to say for two minutes.
你为什么停药了
Why are you off them?
因为它们不起作用
Because they don't work.
那你最初为什么开始用呢
Why were you on them?
因为那药是香蕉口味的
Because they come in banana flavor.
你知道答案的
You know the answer.
你认为治好你的腿就能拯救你的生活
You think fixing your leg will fix your life.
我认为如果生活的一部分  尤其是
I think that my life will be somewhat better
我的腿好一些  我的生活就会好一些
if part of my life, specifically my leg, is somewhat better.
你把你所有的问题都归结为你的腿
You think all your problems are your leg.
你大老远过来  就是为了告诉我
And you're here to tell me that no matter
不管我的腿怎样  生活都会继续郁闷
how depressed I may be, it's not enough.
我认为你希望所有的东西
I think you want everything
都是有形的  简单的
to be physical, tangible, simple.
希望有一剂能治疗不幸的良药
You want unhappiness to have a cure.
豪斯  你显然...
House, you obviously--
我痛恨那个词
I hate that word.
现在我必须得走了
I have to go now.
事实上  并非必须
Actually, I don't,
但是如果一声不吭就离开很没礼貌
but it would be rude to walk out without saying anything.
这个怎么样
What about this?
28岁女性因念珠菌感染
28-year-old woman presenting with burn-like wounds
致口腔及食道多发性灼伤样创面
in her mouth and esophagus from a candidiasis infection.
有意思
Interesting.
如果她也有癫痫症状才和咱们的病人相关
It would also be relevant if the woman had had seizures.
如果有真菌进入她的血流中...
If the fungus had entered her bloodstream--
要是那样  我们会在血检中发现的
We would have seen it in the blood work.
急性髓系白血病
Acute myeloid leukemia
会引起牙龈肿胀
can cause swelling in the gums.
一样  很有意思但是不相关
Again, interesting but not relevant.
我也再说一次  你就是个混蛋
Again, you're being an ass.
她家族里没有血液病史
She doesn't have a history of blood diseases in her family,
她的血细胞计数正常
Her blood count's normal,
而且她没有接触过化学毒素
and she hasn't been exposed to chemical toxins.
是没有就我们所知的毒素
Not that we know of.
她和她男朋友在一起工作
She works most closely with is also her boyfriend.
你觉得如果有化学药品打翻之类的事故
You don't think he would have told us
他会不告诉我们吗
if there had been some sort of chemical spill or accident?
还有一个因素会引起急性髓系白血病
There is one other cause of A.M.L..
等等  你要带她去哪
Wait! Where are you taking her?
我们应该把她带到隔离室
We need to get her into an isolation room
然后为造血干细胞移植手术做准备
and prep for a hematopoietic stem cell transplant.
隔离  为什么
Isolation? Why?
我们认为电离辐射
We think her blood and immune system
摧毁了她的血液和免疫系统
have been destroyed by an exposure to ionizing radiation.
但是我们工作不会接触辐射
But we don't work with radiation.
显然你的女朋友有
Well, apparently your girlfriend does.
不  她没有  你们错了
No, she doesn't. You're wrong.
一定是其它原因
It must be something else.
我们发现你们的公司在研制
We found reports that your company was developing
能摧毁防御地堡的战术核弹头
tactical nuclear warheads for bunker-busting bombs.
在哪看见的  维基解密吗
Where? On wikipedia?
还是有幻想症的白痴的博客
Some paranoid idiot's blog?
我不管你在哪看的  那不是真的
I don't care where you read it. It's not true.
你是说在你们公司里  绝对没有人
You're saying there's absolutely no chance
在你毫不知情的情况下
that anyone in your company is doing
进行一些试验性研究吗
any experimental research that you don't know about?
不  但是我了解温迪  她不会的
No, but I know Wendy and she wouldn't.
你可能并不像你想的那样了解她
Well, maybe you don't know her as well as you thought you did.
请让一下  我们得走了
Excuse me. We have to go.
你需要喝点水
You need a drink.
不用了
I'm fine.
我不是在问你
That wasn't a question.
你真的应该喝点水了
You really do need a drink.
找到一个匹配的
Found a match.
等从捐献者那拿到造血干细胞
We'll start treatment as soon as
我们就立即开始治疗
we get the H.S.C. from the donor.
不会太久的
Shouldn't be long.
塞萨尔在哪
Where's Cesar?
他在等待室
He's in the waiting room.
我想见他
I want to see him.
你不能
You can't.
在你的免疫系统这么差得情况下
It's too dangerous with your immune system
见他是很危险的
this compromised.
他穿着你这样的防护服再进来呢
Why can't he just put on a gown and a mask like you?
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
你接触的人越多
The more people you're exposed to,
感染的几率也就越大
the greater chance of infection.
我很害怕
I'm scared.
我知道
I know.
我们会尽全力的
We're doing everything that we can.
你很快就能和塞萨尔见面了
Cesar will be with you soon.
福曼医生  你该看一下这个
Dr. Foreman, you should look at this.
是什么
What is it?
你的骨盆区疼不疼
You feeling any pain in your pelvic region?
不疼  怎么了
No, why?
你的外阴部充血了
Your genitals... They're engorged.
我要是再喝  我就撑死了
I drink any more, I'm gonna explode.
你不会撑死的
You're not going to explode.
你会癫痫发作
You're just gonna have a seizure,
这证明你的肾脏没有正常工作
which will prove that your kidneys are not working,
就是说在周六晚上  它也没有正常工作
which will also prove that they weren't working Saturday night.
这就是为什么轻轻一击
That's why a glancing body blow
就使你的血压降低
sent your blood pressure into the toilet
也把你打倒在地
and you onto the canvas.
应该要喝多少瓶水
How many bottles is this supposed to take?
六瓶
Six.
那我喝了多少了
And I've drank how many?
八瓶
Eight.
理论并不准确
It's not an exact science.
或者说是  什么都没法证明你是错的
So in other words, nothing's gonna prove you wrong.
你会不停地来折磨骚扰我
You're just gonna keep making me miserable
因为你的生活也不顺
because you're too miserable--
你是个白痴
You're an idiot.
得了  你不会打我的
No, you're not gonna hit me...
因为在你不堪一击的脑袋里
'cause somewhere deep in that way-too-thin skull of yours
你知道自己一无是处
you know that you're full of crap.
这就是你停下慢跑的原因
That's why you stopped jogging for me.
也是你喝八瓶水的原因
That's why you drank eight bottles.
你一方面希望我是错的
Because even though you want to think that I'm wrong
因为这让生活变得简单
'cause it's simpler,
另一方面  你又渴望我是对的
you also desperately want me to be right.
如果我错了
I'm only an ass
给你空筑希望  那我才真是个混蛋
for building your hopes up if I'm wrong.
最后一瓶了
Last one.
你就是个混蛋
You're an ass.
你错了
You were wrong.
这又不是世界末日
It's not the end of the world.
你还想说什么
Anything else you want to say?
你有问题
You have a problem.
我想如果你肯认真看待
I think if you seriously look at everything that--
还想说什么
Anything else?
好了  听着  这不是...
Okay, look, this isn't--
好了  好了
Okay! Okay! Okay! Okay!
不  我没啥要说的
No... I don't.
赶紧出去
Just get out of here.
回家  咱们之后再谈
Go home. We'll talk later.
找一个没有我东西的地方谈
Someplace without any of my stuff.
没什么好谈的
Nothing to talk about.
这才是我想说的
That was my point.
外阴炎症
Inflammation of the genitals
证明我们的推断是错误的
means we were wrong.
多谢你道出了大家的心声
Thanks for the statement of the obvious.
你也是这么想的  不是吗
You'd think so, wouldn't you?
福曼还想坚持辐射中毒的理论
Foreman wants to keep shooting for radiation poisoning.
因为癫痫症状消失了
Because the seizure's have stopped.
因为她不发烧了
Because her fever's gone away.
-因为她好转了  -只是运气而已
- Because she's improved. - By luck.
我病人可不关心因何而好转
I don't think the patient cares.
是  但她还是会死只不过没那么痛苦
Yes, she's gonna die in considerably less discomfort
因为你只是治好了症状
thanks to you treating a few of the symptoms
而不是治愈了她的病
instead of the disease.
-我呼过豪  -闭嘴
- I paged ho-- - Shut up.
你喝醉了
You're drunk.
这算是谁的错呢
Well, whose fault is that?
再给我杯苏格兰威士忌
Give me another scotch.
我不能再卖酒给你了
I can't serve you.
因为我是黑人吗
This 'cause I'm black?
但我不是  所以
Cause I'm not, so...
兄弟  别这样
Come on, buddy.
是你先卖给我酒  让我喝醉了
Look, you can't get me drunk and then
现在又唠叨  不让我喝
give me crap for being drunk.
这跟和甩了别人以后
That's like dumping someone
还假惺惺地安慰她  有什么不同
and then giving them crap for being upset.
这可不是什么高尚的行为
That's just not decent.
我来解释下大家为什么来这里
Let me explain why people come here.
他们是过来喝酒的
They come here to drink.
于是我们就要问了  为什么人们要喝酒
Which causes us to ask, why do people drink?
酒是粮食吗
Is it sustenance?
不是  它好喝吗
No. Is it taste?
-不好喝  -别混蛋了
- No. - Don't be a jerk.
是为了见这些所谓勇敢的酒友吗
Is it the company of stout-hearted men?
我觉得不是
I don't think so.
它能抚平痛苦吗
Is it killing pain?
没错
Yes.
7.5%的酒精能帮你抚平伤口
7 1/2% life duller.
这就是酒吧的实质
That's the business you're in.
人们以喝酒来发泄对世界的怨气
You're in the "Screw the world" business.
喝醉了  就能暂时逃避现实
You're in the "Reality sucks
醉生梦死一番
and fantasy temporarily appears to not suck" business.
就给这白痴一杯酒吧  让他闭嘴
Just get the moron a drink so he'll shut the hell up.
不要
No.
-我给你酒了啊  -你没有尊严吗
- I'm giving you your drink. - Have you no pride?
你可以选择给或者不给
Either serving me is a good idea or it's a bad idea.
但不能为了"让我闭嘴"这种烂理由
Shutting me up is a crappy reason
而对你的信念妥协
for compromising what you believe.
很显然  就这样你也不会闭嘴
Not even an effective one apparently.
我是不是得揍他了啊
Am I gonna have to hit him?
这不是个好主意
Not a good idea.
但如果这么做才是正确的呢
But what if it's the right thing to do?
妥协永远不是解决之道
Compromise is never the answer.
站起来
Stand up.
我会让你击第一拳
I will allow you to throw the first punch.
坐下
Sit down.
我不会打你的
I'm not gonna hit you.
太好了  其实我刚是骗你的
Just as well, 'cause I was lying.
你可以不用担心了
You can relax.
她开始好转了吗
She's getting better?
坏消息是  因为你一直在她身边
Bad news is, because of your extended exposure to her
和她在一起工作
and her workplace,
我们也要对你进行治疗
we're gonna need to treat you as well.
我感觉很好啊
I feel fine.
不幸的是  这是处理辐射中毒的规定
Unfortunately that's the way it can be with radiation.
等有症状出现再治疗  就太晚了
No symptoms until it's too late to do anything.
你将需要骨髓移植
You're gonna need a bone marrow transplant.
-不  -骨髓移植确实会给你带来
- No. - A marrow transplant does leave you exposed
感染各种疾病的危险
to all sorts of illnesses,
但真的没有别的好办法了
but there really is no choice here.
她并没有辐射中毒
She doesn't have radiation poisoning.
她正在好转
She's getting better.
在情况变遭之前
We need to start your treatment
我们要开始你的治疗
before it's too late.
不
No.
你要不然是有自杀倾向
You're either suicidal
要不然就是知道我们是错的
or you know we're wrong.
而你之所以会如此确信  我们诊断错了
And the only way you could know for sure
是因为你知道令她垂死的真正病因
what wasn't killing her is if you knew what was.
而且你确实知道  不是吗
And you do, don't you?
因为就是你下的毒
Because you've been poisoning her
而她好转的原因就是
and the reason she's getting better
你不在她身边了
is because you haven't been near her.
我们的同事正在去你家的路上
Our co-workers are on their way
去搜寻毒药
to your home right now to search for poisons.
别再浪费大家的时间了吧
You mind saving them the trouble?
谋杀未遂总比谋杀好
Attempted murder is better than murder.
你在这里干什么
What are you doing here?
为我的决胜之战进行训练
Training for my big fight.
只需要你
Just need you to--
再喝五瓶水吗
Drink five more bottles?
再被揍几拳吗
Get punched a few more times?
你就放弃吧  赶紧滚吧
Look, just get out and give up.
只有你才会临阵退缩
That's your specialty.
你这决胜之战看来是没戏了
Looks like you already lost your big fight.
听着  我也许被别人揍一拳就倒了
Look, I may not be able to take a punch,
但我还是能揍你的
but I can still throw one.
三  二
Three, two...
今天真是太美好了
What a lovely day.
塞萨尔在哪里
Where's Cesar?
在监狱里
In jail.
他企图谋杀你
He was trying to kill you.
他发现你和格伦的事情了
He found out about you and Glenn,
他承认他本不该觉得惊讶的
which, he admitted, shouldn't have surprised him
因为他开始和你约会时
since he started seeing you
你还在和托尼约会
while you were dating Tony.
他对我投毒吗
He poisoned me?
反复地  用的是斑蝥
Repeatedly... with spanish fly.
所含的活性斑蝥素是种强效毒药
The active ingredient cantharidin is a potent toxin
会引起很多和辐射类似的症状
and can cause a lot of the same damage as radiation.
他竟然对我投毒吗
He poisoned me?
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
他是能通过安全检查的
He had a security clearance.
这是什么
What's this?
一个手掌
A palm.
可以做很多事情
Useful for many things.
鼓掌  涂油
Slapping, greasing,
可能还有其它用途
probably some other applications too.
现在它准备好拿回那50块
Right now it's ready for $50
再羞辱你一番
and humiliation.
他真的病了吗
He was actually sick?
他不是被击倒的
He wasn't knocked out by the punch.
是因为在那拳之前  他被对手用臂钳住
He was knocked out by the clinch before the punch.
对手在他颈后打了一拳
Took a shot to the back of the neck.
更具体地说  是血管球瘤导致的
More specifically, to an abnormal growth of nerves
神经的异常生长
caused by a glomus tumor.
就好比体内有把泰瑟枪[高压电击枪]
Kind of like a built-in taser.
对他全身造成了巨大的冲击
Sent a massive shock to his entire body,
使所有器官都不工作了
shut everything down.
真难以置信
Fascinating.
完美地解释了他输掉的原因
Completely explains exactly how he lost.
你最好别用这种口气说话
Oh, you are not gonna be like that,
因为你这还有很多海报能让我砸
'cause you got a lot more posters here.
不  我没那个意思
No, I'm not.
豪斯  干得好
Well done, House.
你可能救了这个人一命
You might have saved that guy.
帮他起死回生了
Given him his life back.
没有  他需要手术
Oh, no. He needs surgery.
他再也不能打拳击了
He's never gonna fight again.
你的眼睛怎么了
What happened to your eye?
你还好吧
You okay?
好极了
Better than okay.
黑暗中的双眸  正注视着你*
*'Cause that unseen eye is watching you
请别让你的右手*
*Please don't let your right hand
知晓你左手的行动*
*Know what your left hand do
我只配给你提靴拿鞋*
*I'm just trying to put your boots on you
追捧在你身后  女人*
*And hip you, woman
黑暗中的双眸  正注视着你*
*'cause that unseen eye is watching you